（忆往昔）
快抱着你弟弟跑出去
Take your brother outside as fast as you can.
快 Dean 快跑
Now, Dean, go.
你还记得什么
What else do you remember.
没什么 我那时候也小 好吗
Nothing.I was a kid, all right.
- 最重要的是 - 照顾好Sammy
- Most important - Watch out for Sammy.
照顾你
Watching out for you.
是我生命中的一部分
It's kinda who I am.
我有个哥哥
I got this brother, right.
他总是告诉我
When he always tell me how.
他会好好照顾我
He's gonna watch our for me.
吃晚饭吧
Now, eat your dinner.
你的蔬菜
You can get your vegetables.
你怎么敢想 我会把任何别的事
Don't you dare think that there's anything.
看得比你更重要
That I would put in front of you.
Sammy受伤了
Sammy's hurt.
伤的很严重
He's hurt real bad.
我治疗Sam的同时 也在治疗我自己
I heal Sam while I healing myself.
我每用一下我的力量
Every time I use my power.
自己身体状况就会减弱
It weakens me.
你经历了试炼
You went to the trials.
我就是觉得 你最好
I just think it's better if.
慢慢来
We took it easy, you know.
你这么精力旺盛 就像是
And didn't act like you are.
被天使附身了一样
Possessed by an angel.
（如今）
等等
Wait up.
快
Hurry.
他就在我们后面
He's right behind us.
（赫利威尔 纽约州）
快快 赶快
Come on.Come on.Hurry.
快进去 关门
Go, go.Close it.
别闹了好吗 说好的
Come on, guys.The barn is a.
仓库不是捉迷藏的范围啊
A no-fly zone during hide-and-go seek.
小屁孩儿们
Boys.
快出来 小坏蛋们
Come on, you delinquents.
该睡觉了
Time for bed.
好了 孩子们 游戏结束了
All right.Game's over, boys.
快出来
Let's bring it in.
10分钟前就熄灯了
Lights out was 10 minutes ago.
一帮小混蛋
You little bastards.
好了 我要
Okay, I'm gonna.
等我数到10
You got till the count of 10.
你们最好全出来 不然叫你们好看
And you'd better come out or the beIt's coming off.
One.
不是吧
Come on.
是你们干的吗
Boys.
别闹了
Come on.
这一点都不好玩儿
This isn't funny.
Dean
Dean.
Kevin
Kevin.
喂
Hello.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
我不认识 不认识什么D犬
There's no…There's no D-Dog.
给我
I got it.I got it.
Sonny 嘿 有事儿吗
Sonny, hey, so what's up.
哦
Okay.
好的 你小心些
All right, yeah, just sit tight.
我马上就过去
I'll be there as soon as I can.
嗯
Yep.
怎么回事 D犬
So, what was that all about, D-Dog.
你还记不记得 很久以前
You remember when we were kids.
有一年春天我们在纽约州的北边
That spring in Upstate, New York.
老爸去猎食人怪
Dad was on a rugaru hunt.
我们 我们住进了一个租来的小房子里
We…we crashed the bungalow colony.
- 里面只有乒乓球桌 - 记得
- With the ping pong table - Yeah.
我记得后来你不见了
Yeah, you disappeared.
我回来的时候你就没影儿了
I came back you were gone and.
然后老爸把我送去Bobby家待了好几个月
He shift me off to Bobby's for a couple of months.
他找你找了好久
And went and found you.
说是什么在一次猎魔中失踪了之类的
You were lost in a hunt or something.
对 我们是这么跟你说的
That's what we told you.Right.
什么 什么叫这么跟我说的
I'm sorry.That's what you told me.
事实是
Truth is.
老爸留下的饭钱
I lost food money that dad.
我打牌输光了
Left for us in a card game.
我知道等你饿了的时候就没办法了
I knew you'd get hungry so.
所以我就想从当地一个市场
I tried to take in the 5 finger discount.
顺手牵牵羊 但是被发现了
At local market and got busted.
我不是去猎魔了
I wasn't on a hunt.
我被送去一个少年之家
They sent me to a boy's home.
少年之家吗 就是
A boy's home?Like a.
少管所一类的吗
Reform school.
嗯 差不多
Yeah, more or less.
那是一个农场 负责人是Sonny
It was a farm and a guy ran it, Sonny.
他 他很照顾我
He…He looked after me.
等下 Sonny知道我们是干什么的吗
Wait, does Sonny know what we do.
对 他人不错
Yeah, he's good people.
后来我把备用手机的手机号给他了
I gave hime the number of bat phone and.
貌似他现在遇到我们管的事儿了
Sounds like he's got something on our wheelhouse.
就这样
So.
那个
Hey.
你觉得这次自己行吗
Think you're gonna be cool to do this.
还是你太累了
Or you get too tired.
没有 嗯 我只是
No…yeah, I'm just.
我没事
I'll be fine.
大家对去
And everybody's okay with.
卡茨斯基都没意见吗
Heading out to the Catskill.
这儿就我一个人
I'm everybody.
嗯
Yeah.
好吧好吧
Right, all right.
收拾好自己的行李 准备出发
Grab your stuff.We'll head out.
嘿 Dean
Hey, Dean.
那个
I mean.
为什么当时 你不直接说
Why didn't you just tell me.
- 你去了少年之家 - 不知道
- You went to a boy's home - I don't know.
是老爸编的
It was dad's idea.
然后就
And then it just.
整件事就变成那样了
You know…story became the story.
我那时候才16岁
I was 16.
你就在这儿
You were here.
待了两个月 老爸都没找到你
For 2 months, and dad couldn't find you.
不是 他找到我了
Oh no, he found me.
他很快就找到我了
He found me quick.
但是他把我扔这儿了 因为我把钱输光了
But he left me here, cause I lost the money.
你才16 16的孩子都会犯错
You were 16 and you made mistake.
对 是我犯的错
Yeah, I made the mistake.
我知道你在想什么
I know how you think.
这跟老爸没关系
None of this was dad's fault.
嗨
Hi.
有什么事吗
What can I do for you boys.
我是Dean
I'm Dean.
这是我弟弟 Sam
This is my brother, Sam.
我们是Sonny的老朋友
We're old buddies of Sonny's.
狱友吗
Prison buddies.
不是
No.
能告诉他我们到了吗
Do you mind telling him we're here.
我去找他
I'll go get him.
地是刚拖的
Just mop this floor.
脏鞋什么的都不许踩
You take off those road stunters.
他有前科
So he's an ex-con.
不然呢 善良的天使吗
What he would?Such an angel.
相信我 他比天使要好很多
Trust me.He's more than made up for it.
Steve Hewlett把他
Steve Hewlett caught him.
抓了个人赃俱获
Right-handed.
就在他的店里
Stealing up at his store.
他偷了什么
So, what did he take.
花生酱和面包
Get this.Peanut butter and bread.
好吧
Okay.
跟家属联系了吗
And how about family.
他爸打电话了
Well, his old man called.
他爸知道真相以后 扔下话说
Once he found out what happened.
让他在监狱里自生自灭好了
He said let him rot in jail.
法官休假去了
Judge's off on a fishing trip.
这孩子又太小 用不着闹到县里去
Boy's too young to leave in county, so.
他最好待在这儿等着下一步的传讯
Thought he best stay here till arraignment.
我没意见
I don't see why not, man.
谢了 Sonny
Appreciate it, Sonny.
黑眼圈怎么来的
Where did you get the shiner.
你觉得很可笑吗
You think that's funny.
我觉得你反应太慢了
I think you're slow.
是你他妈动的手
You sucker punched me.
- 那是你的荣幸 - 好了好了
- You wish - Come on, now.
Billy 我来
Billy, I got this, buddy.
没事的
It's alright.
- 你不该那么说 - 是吗
- You shouldn't do that, kid - Yeah.
为什么 就因为他是警察吗
Why?'Cause he's a cop.
因为他一不高兴
Because when you make him mad.
就带着钥匙走人了
He leaves with the key.
别紧张
Don't sweat it.
警察弄的吗
Deputy do that.
还是你爸
Or your old man.
怎么来的
Well then how did you get it.
狼人
Werewolf.
好吧
Okay.
那
So.
你怎么知道我不会逃跑
How do you know I won't just run away.
因为你很饿
Because you're hungry.
我不饿
No, I'm not.
那你为什么去偷花生酱和面包
Why do you steal bread and peanut butter.
这地方到底是干什么的
So, what is this place anyway.
收留你这样的孩子
It's for boys like you.
给农场干干活
You work the land.
教你守纪律 懂得尊敬别人
Teaches you some discipline responsibility.
还能让你避开麻烦
Keep you out of trouble.
真弱
That's lame.
比监狱要好
Beats jail.
来 我给你找些吃的
Come on, I'll fix you something to eat.
- D犬 - Sonny
- D-dog - Sonny.
- 见到你真好 - 我也是
- Good to see you - You too, bro.
这肯定就是Sam了
This must be Sam.
很高兴见到你
Good to meet you.
我也是
Back at you, brother.
看上去
So.
农场经营的 不错
Farm looks…nice.
得了吧 勉勉强强而已
Oh please, man's barely standing.
现在也只有几个孩子在这儿
I only got a handful kids work around here, now.
为什么
Why is that.
因为现在他们更喜欢直接把孩子们关起来
Because these days, the system'd rather.
而不是给他们救赎的机会
Incarcerate a boy than redeem him.
那个 Sonny
Hey, Sonny.
我们可以单独谈谈吗
You mind if we talk alone.
Ruth
Hey Ruth.
你能去看看孩子们吗
Would you please go check on the boys.
看看他们的早间杂务做完没有
Make sure their morning chores are getting done.
好吧 出什么事儿了
All right, so, what's happening.
还记得Jack吗
You remember Jack, don't you.
嗯 那个前海军陆战员老顽固
Yeah, the tough old leatherneck.
不知怎的 一天晚上
Well, somehow, that ancient rusty broken down.
那台破拖拉机突然活了过来
Tractor just roared to life.
冲着他就扎过去了
And run him over the other night.
可能 也许只是
Maybe…maybe just a.
可能它只是从车位里滑了出来
Slipped out of park or something.
不可能
Couldn't have.
我 我从来都
You know I never…never believe in.
不相信你们这一行
This mumbo jumbo stuffs you boys into, but.
不过 情况不大对劲
Something ain't right.
什么意思
What do you mean.
就是
Well, just.
发生了好多事
Things start happening.
灯光闪烁不定
You know, lights flickering on and off.
墙里面传出奇怪的抓墙声
Strange scratch sounds coming from inside the walls.
窗户和门突然自己关上
Windows and doors slamming.
我们四处看看的时候
All right, you think you can round up the boys.
你能帮忙把孩子们集中到一起吗
When we take a look around.
没问题
That shouldn't be a problem.
他们大部分都回家休假了
Most are home on break.
除了那些无家可回的
Well, except those with no home to go into.
你去查查这房子
Why don't you take the house.
我去仓库看看
I'll check the barn.
好
Yeah.
我很抱歉
Hey, I'm so sorry.
我还以为 我
I…I thought I.
看到什么了 就
Saw something and.
看到鬼魂吗
Like…like a ghost.
Sonny说你们是老朋友 但是
Sonny told me you were old friends, but.
我知道你们来的真正目的
I know why you're really here.
所以我才为我们大家祈祷
That's why I was praying for us.
祈祷什么
Praying for what.
祈祷在此作怪的恶灵离开
For the ghosts that haunted this farm to leave.
好吧 鬼马小精灵
All right, Casper.
你在哪儿呢
Where are you at.
有人吗
Hello.
有人在吗
Anybody here.
嘿 你一个人在这儿干什么
Hey kid, what're you doing here by yourself.
打怪
Fighting monsters.
什么样的怪
What kind of monsters.
什么样的都有
All sort with the.
和打怪达人Bruce一起
Bruce the monster smasher.
那是条披风吗
Is that a cape.
披着披风打架可不怎么方便啊
Little impractical for smashing monsters.
你有可能会被闷死
You know you can choke.
我铲除邪恶势力
I clutter evil.
我信你
I bet you do.
我是Dean
I'm Dean.
我是Timmy
Timmy.
这样
Let's try it again.
你长大肯定是个男子汉
You're gonna be a man.
那就要像男子汉一样握手
You learn to shake like one, okay.
用你最大的力气抓紧我的手
So, give me your best kung fu grip.
很好
Good.
然后看着我的眼睛
Then look me straight in the eye.
让我知道你是认真的
And let me know you mean business.
能使多大劲就使多大劲
Shake as hard as you can.
这才像话
That's it.
学会了这么握手 你就会没事儿的
You shake like that, you'll be all right.
Timmy你认识那个
Hey, Timmy do you know.
在这儿工作的Jack吗
Jack who worked here.
你能跟我说说他吗
What can you tell me about him.
他一直在喊
He yelled a lot.
他出事儿的时候一直在喊
He was yelling when he has his accident.
你怎么知道
How do you know that.
他出事儿的时候
Cause me and the other boys.
我和其他男孩子在附近玩儿
Were playing here when it happened.
你看到什么了吗
Did you see anything.
关于那天晚上
Is there anything else about that night.
你还能记得什么 任何事情都可以
That you can remember, anything at all.
突然之间
Suddenly.
变得很冷
It got really cold.
我能走了吗
Can I go.
要是不赶紧完成我的活儿
I have to finish my chores.
Ruth太太会很生气的
Before Mrs.Ruth gets mad.
Ruth管的很严吧
That Ruth, she runs a tight ship.
你赶紧回去吧
Yeah, you'd better roll.
我在这个镇子里长大
I grew up in this town.
我小时候经常来这个农场
I used to come up here as a little girl.
Wasserlaufs一家
The Wasserlaufs.
Howard和Doreen
Howard and Doreen.
他们曾经是这儿的主人
They used to own this farm back then.
我的同事Jack
My coworker Jack.
希望他安息
May he rest in peace.
他是这儿的农场工人
He worked here as a farm hand.
Howard是个好人 但是
Howard was a nice man but.
是在他酗酒之前
But when he didn't get into that corn liquor.
有一天他神经质的坚信
One night he got into his thick skull that.
Jack跟他老婆Doreen上床了
Jack and his wife Dereine were rolling around in the hey.
这当然不是真的 但是
It wasn't true but.
Howard太多疑了
Howard is paranoid's got the better of them.
他试图杀了他们两个
He tried to kill them both.
Jack逃走了 但是Doreen
Jack got away but Doreen.
他杀了她
He killed her.
用一根铁钩
With the meat cliver.
被判进了监狱
Got life in jail.
但Howard在一年前就死了
Which for Howard ended a year ago.
他总是发誓一定要找Jack报仇
He always swore he'd get his revenge on poor Jack.
看来他得手了
Looks like he finally got it.
Howard的尸体埋在镇子里吗
Is Howard buried here in town.
这么说
So.
爸不想让你告诉我真相
Dad didn't want you to tell me.
为什么呢
How come.
那地方真的那么不好吗
Is this place really so bad.
我都不怎么记得了
I don't even remember.
听着
Look.
没有人对我动手动脚
Nobody bad touched me.
没人用烟头烫我
Nobody burned me with their smokes or.
或者用衣架抽我
Beat me with a metal hanger.
所以没什么不好的
I call that a win.
嘿
Hey.
好了 咱们该把这家伙送西天了
All right, let's barbecue old McDonald here.
早烧早超生
Get the hell outta dodge.
你还好吗
Are you okay.
出什么事儿了
What's wrong.
开门啊
Open up.
Ruth
Ruth.
Cus餐馆
Cus's Place.
没关系
That's okay.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
Dean 你知道 我完全可以
Dean, you know I'm fine just.
拿了汉堡去别的地方
Grab a burger and to go somewhere right.
不要一份史上最美味的香蕉薄饼吗
What?Miss the best banana pancakes you ever had.
- 谢谢 - 没事儿
- Thanks - No problem.
只要来这儿超过几个月
Only these for the boys.
我都带他们来这儿
After they've been here for months.
我是说谢谢你帮我撤销控诉
I meant for getting the charges against me dropped.
饿肚子不犯法
Well, being hunger is not a crime.
但偷东西就犯法了
It's stealing that is but.
如果你日后不再犯错
I feel if you only do that once.
没必要留下案底
You don't deserve a record.
鉴于我们没法联系到你老爸
And since we can't find your pops anywhere.
你可以想住多久住多久 Dean
You can stay here as long as you want, Dean.
你在学校表现很出色 交到了新朋友
You're doing good in school, you making friends.
还加入了摔跤队
You made the wrestling team.
我为你感到骄傲
I'm proud of you.
我问你几件事儿
Let me ask you something.
我希望你能对我有话直说
I want you to be straight with me.
你是不是在搞什么
Are you into thie whole.
阴暗的恶魔崇拜思想
Heavy metal devil worship stuff.
什么
What.
没有
No.
我不是 我不是有偏见什么的
I'm not-I'm not judging.
只是我发现
It's just I found a few.
你的床柱上刻着几个标志
Occult-looking symbols carving in your bedpost.
说来话长
It's a very long story.
那么这个故事能解释为什么
Is this story have anything to do why you put salt.
每晚睡觉前 你都会在房间门口撒盐吗
In front of your bunk door every night before bed.
这是我们的家务事
Well, it's a family thing so.
我不想多说
I can't really talk about it.
是那个把你扔在这儿的那个家吗
The same family that left you here.
你 你怎么了
What are-what are you.
不好意思说还是别的什么
In a mob or something.
别的什么
More like something.
我以前是个混帮派的 记得吧
I was part of this gang, right.
他们都是我家人
They were my family.
我活的很自在
I lived free.
为了我们的帮派 我甚至可以去死
I would've been died for it.
知道最后怎么了吗
You know where got me.
我在监狱待了15年
15 years in a correctional facility.
为了什么
And for what.
忠诚吗
Being loyal.
对谁忠诚
To who.
我应该忠诚于自己
I should've been loyal to myself.
Dean 因为如果真的有变节
Because you get one shot in this game, Dean.
你照镜子的时候
And when you look into the mirror.
你希望镜子里的人 不是别人 就是自己
You want the guy to look back at you to be his own man.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
嘿 Robin 你怎么样
Hey, Robin, how are you.
我很好 你呢
I'm good, how are you.
不错
Good.
来见见我农场的小工头 Dean
Meet my new ranch foreman here, Dean.
Robin
Robin.
欢迎来到Cus餐馆 两位想来点儿什么
Welcome to Cus's, what can I get you two.
我猜你一定没想到能在这儿见到我
Bet you never thought you'd see me here.
我现在有点儿忙
Look, I'm a little bit of slammed right now.
你们不来点儿今日特供吗
Don't yu guys here for the specials.
Robin
Robin.
Dean Winchester
Dean Winchester.
住在Sonny那儿的那个
Used to live up at Sonny's.
抱歉
Look, sorry there's just.
在Sonny那儿住过的孩子太多了
There's so many boys that passed through there.
我不可能记住所有
It's hard to remember every.
所有人和名字
Every name and face.
好吧
Yeah.
抱歉 我就是
No, sorry, I just have been.
我记得你跟你妈妈经常去
Remember you coming up there with your mom.
她教孩子们弹吉他 很久以前的事儿了
She'd give guitar lesson that's a long ago.
是啊 我妈妈
Yeah, mom.
她总是喜欢帮助那些男孩子
She loved helping out the boys.
所以
I guess that's why.
她去世之后 我接替了她的工作
I kept giving lessons after she passed.
嘿 Robin
Hey, Robin.
抱歉 我去去就回
Would you excuse me, I'll be right back.
- 哥们儿 - 走
- Dude - Let's go.
怎么
What.
怎么回事儿
What was that.
没什么
Nothing.
还没什么
很明显 绝对有什么
Well, obviously, there was something.
那个女招待是谁
Who is that waitress.
我说过了 没什么
I said it was nothing, all right.
别再提了
Drop it.
Sonny
Sonny.
什么
What.
我想冲进去救她
I tried to get in and save her.
但该死的 那门就是打不开
But the damn door wouldn't open.
锁上了吗
Locked.
农场里的门根本没有装锁
There was no locks on the farm.
看来我们之前
That means our little field trip.
找错人了
To the cemetery was a bust.
Sonny 你能想起不对劲的地方吗
Sonny is there anything else weird you could remember.
怎么 都这样了难道还有更不对劲的吗
What?'Cause we're not chest-deep in weird already, boys.
我明白 我明白 但是
I know, I know, I mean.
任何细节都行
Anything, really.
有一件事儿
There was one thing.
Ruth总是带着她的念珠
Ruth always had her rosery beads with her.
但是我现在找不到它了
But now I can't find them anywhere.
好吧
All right.
咱们从受害者开始分析
Start with the vics, OK.
他们都住在这儿
I mean they both lived in the house.
平时都跟这群男孩子们走得很近
They both worked close with the boys.
不如我去找他们谈谈
Why don't I go can have a chat with the rug rats.
问问情况
I'll see what's up.
好吧
Yeah.
Sonny 你有被害员工的个人记录吗
Sonny, you got any employee records of the victims.
在我办公室里
My office.
我带你去拿
Let's do it.
你想怎么样啊
Come on, what you gonna do about it.
要开始哭了吗
Are you gonna cry.
Timmy你个小怪胎
Timmy you're such a little weirdo.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
你们在干什么
What're you doing.
过来
Come here.
我们什么都没干
Nothing.
Timmy 怎么回事
Timmy, what's going on.
听着 你们两个
All right, you two.
今天早晨Ruth出事儿的时候
Where were you this morning.
你们在哪儿
When Ruth had her accident.
除非你是个警察
Unless you're a cop.
不然我们不用告诉你任何事情
We don't need to tell you anything.
好吧
Oh, okay, well.
怎么样
How about that.
我们早上根本不在这儿
We weren't even here this morning.
Sonny让我们去城里买鸡饲料
Sonny sent us to town to get some chicken feed.
我们发誓
We swear.
那Ruth呢
What about Ruth.
你们知道些什么
What can you tell me about her.
我们都管她叫戒律长
We used to call her the warden.
她总是拿圣经说事儿
She was a real bible-thumping hard-ass.
很显然
Obviously.
还有什么吗
What else.
有什么不同寻常或者奇怪的事儿
Anything different or weird.
有没有想起来什么
You can think of.
你是问 除了怪胎Timmy之外的吗
You mean, besides Timmy.
嘿
Hey.
你们俩谁要是敢再动他
Either of you touch him ever again.
我就对你们俩不客气了
I'm gonna go all Guantanamo on you.
听明白了吗
Understand me.
现在赶紧给我滚
Get the hell out of here.
快滚
Go on, get.
嘿
Hey.
你和Bruce都没事儿吧
You and Bruce okay.
没事儿
Yeah.
听我说
Listen to me.
这种人其实都是懦夫
Guys like that they are cowards.
明白吗
Okay.
你只要反击一次
All you gotta do is stand up to'em one time.
他们就再也不敢了
And they'll stop.
我保证
I promise.
好吧
Okay.
嘿 Sonny 等等
Hey, Sonny, wait.
这都是什么
What is all this.
这都是我们的荣耀
It's all our hall of fame.
来这儿的 有很多都是很出色的运动员
We had some pretty great athletes come through here.
包括你哥哥
Including your brother.
他赢了61公斤级摔跤比赛
He was Sullivan county in 135 pound wrestling champion.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
我随时都能泡上她
She can give me lessens any time.
她太老了
Gross.She's like ancient.
什么玩意儿
What the hell.
这玩意儿怎么跑到这里面去了
What's this doing in there.
那孩子估计得缝上8000针
Kid's gonna need 8000 stiches.
但是还能喘气
But he'll be fine.
那孩子之前在欺负Timmy 对吧
The kid was bullying Timmy before the accident, right.
没错 怎么了
Yeah, why.
看看这个
Check this out.
Timmy是在一座废弃的房子里被发现的
Timmy was found in an abbandoned building.
大概一年前 只有他一个人
About a year ago by himself.
没人知道他在那里待了多久
No one was sure how long he'd been there.
他父母呢
What about his parents.
当时在网上发了照片
They posted a pictures on the internet.
但谁都没出现过
But no one ever showed up.
那他为什么在这儿
Then what's he doing here.
他不应该去孤儿院之类的地方吗
Shouldn't he be in like an orphanage.
他一直从儿童服务中心逃跑
He kept running away from child services.
大概在3个月前
So about 3 months ago.
Sonny才把他带回来
Sonny offered to take him in.
好吧 惹人厌的管理员
All right, so hard-ass counselors.
欺负人的坏孩子都成了受害者
Bullies all bite to dust.
但Timmy还在
But Timmy's standing.
那咱们要找的是什么
So what are we talking about.
一只愤怒的Damian吗
We got ourselves a Damian on our hands.
不 EMF的数据显示不是
No, EMF rules out a demon.
有可能是鬼魂附身
Probably ghost possession.
怎么
Meaning what.
直接一把盐灌Timmy嘴里
We find Timmy and shove a fistful of.
强迫鬼魂离开吗
Salt down his throat, forced ejection.
这次换你去检查仓库
You're taking the barn this time.
听说你去过很多地方
So you've been to a lot of places.
是啊 我
Yeah, My.
我爸喜欢游荡四方
My dad likes to move around a lot.
你爸做什么的
What your dad do.
很无聊的事情
Boring stuff.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it.
不 不喜欢
No.Not really.
但是我爸想让我接管他的事业
But my dad expects me to follow his footsteps.
所以 我已经习惯了
So…I've kinda gotten used to it.
嗯 我懂
Yeah, I get it.
我爸也让我接管餐馆
My pops wants me to take over the diner.
但是 是不会成真的
But that's not happening.
那 你想干什么
So, what do you really want to do.
我想当摄影师
I wanna be a photographer.
一起周游世界
See the world.
去一些很稀奇的地方 品尝各种食物
Go to strange lands, eat crazy food.
我想当摇滚明星 不过
I wanna be a rock star, but.
我也很喜欢车
I also really like cars.
机械工似乎很辛苦
Being a mechanic seems rough.
什么 不 才不呢
What?No, no, not at all.
所有的汽车都非常酷
Cars are freaking cool as hell.
修理他们就像解谜语
Fixing them is like a puzzle.
还有 最酷的地方就是
And the best part is.
等你修完了
When you're done.
它们就走了 你不需要负责
They leave, you're not responsible for them any more.
你亲过女生吗
Have you kissed many girls.
什么 当然 亲过很多
What?Yeah, of course.Lots.
真的
Really.
这么说来 我们需要更多的练习
Well, I guess we'll just have to keep practising.
哦 嘿
Oh, hey.
在餐厅的时候你们怎么了
What happen to you at the diner.
我刚要回头给你们点菜
I turned around to take your order.
你们就消失了
You were just gone.
这话长了
Long story.
你看见Timmy了吗
Have you seen Timmy.
还没
No not yet.
不过他应该马上就来上吉他课了
But he should be here any minute for his guitar lesson.
对 但是他的课得取消了
Yeah, we're gonna cancel that.
什么
What.
我们现在就要离开市里
We gotta get out of there, okay.
我没时间给你解释 你只需要相信我
I don't have time to explain.You just gotta trust me.
相信你
Trust you.
为何我还要再相信你
And why would I do that again.
你的确记得我
You do remember me.
我怎么能忘
How could I forget.
怎么了
What's wrong.
我希望能永远这样
I just hope this lasts.
我又不去哪里
I'm not going anywhere, you know.
是 就听你说
Yeah, says you.
我不能走
Well, I can't.
要不谁带你去学校的舞会
Who else will take you to the school dance.
这是你在邀请我当你的舞伴吗
Is this your way of asking me to be your date.
Dean Winchester
Dean Winchester.
是啊 我的表现怎么样
Yeah, how am I doing so far.
我是逼不得已才走
There were reasons why I had to leave.
现在我没时间解释给你解释
I don't have time to explain them to you right now.
我得带你马上离开这里
I gotta get you out of here.
嘿 你干什么
Hey, what are you doing.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起什么
Sorry about what Timmy.
我停不下来了
I can't stop it.
走 快走
Go go go.
Sam 快走
Sam go.
锁住了 靠
Locked.Damn it.
画圈
Circle.
Dean 刚才发生了什么
Dean, what just happened in there.
听我说
OK, listen to me.
不管发生什么 你都待在这个圈里面不要动
Whatever happens, you stay inside of this circle.
- 明白了么 - 好了
- Understood - All right.
Dean
Dean.
我控制不了她
I can't control her.
你控制不了谁
You can't control who.
你母亲 对吧
Your mom, right.
Timmy 听我说
Timmy, listen.
跟我们讲讲那场火的事情 好吗
We need you tell us about the fire, OK.
那时很晚
It was late.
我们开车回家路上撞进了树丛
We were driving home when we crashed in the woods.
周围所有东西都着火了
Everything was on fire, but.
她救了我
She saved me.
她把我推出车外
Pushed me out.
之后她和车一起爆炸了
Before the car blew up with her in it.
但是这不是故事的全部 对吧
But that's not all, was it.
我跑进树丛里
I ran through the woods.
看见了个闲置的房子 就躲了进去
And found an empty building where I hid.
我很害怕 周围又冷又黑
I was scared.It was dark and cold.
所以我就哭了
So I cried.
哭喊着我妈
I cried for my mom.
然后她就出现了
And then, she came.
但是她变了 对吗
But she changed, right.
我猜是她给你的那个玩偶对吧
I bet she gave you that cool action figure.
在我九岁生日的时候给我的
Yeah, when I turned nine.
Timmy 把那个玩偶给我吧
Timmy, I'm gonna need that action figure.
不要
No.
我铲除邪恶势力
I clobber evil.
看来并不是这个玩偶
It looks it wasn't the action figure.
牵扯着她留在这里不走
That was anchoring her here, Dean.
那是什么
Then what is.
他
Him.
我觉得
You know what.
他母亲不走或许是
Maybe his mom can't let go.
还在另一个世界保护着他
And she is still protecting him from the grave.
保护他远离什么
Protecting him from what?From us.
也许她分不清楚什么是真的威胁
Maybe she doesn't know what threats are real.
什么是假的 所以攻击一切
And what's not, so she just attacks all of them.
好吧
Great.
所以呢 除了杀了他就再没别的办法了吗
So what?unless we waste the kid, we are sitting ducks.
这 这太疯狂了
This is, this is crazy.
Robin Robin
Robin, Robin.
靠
Damn it.
- Robin等等 - 你到底是谁
- Robin, wait - Who are you.
现在唯一的任务就是保证你的安全
Right now the only thing is keeping you safe.
Timmy 我们需要你的帮助
Timmy, we're gonna need your help okay.
听我说 我希望你集中注意力
Listen to me, I need you to focus, okay.
我们不是来伤害你的
Look we are not here to hurt you.
Sammy
Sammy.
我阻止不了她
I can't stop her.
Timmy 你必须阻止她
Timmy, you have to try.
是因为你哭喊她 她才出现的
She came to you when you cried out for her.
你必须要告诉她离开
And you have to tell her to stop and go away.
- 她是我妈 - 她是个鬼魂
- She is my mom - She is a ghost.
Timmy 因为她放不下你 现在成疯了
Timmy, because she can't move on, she is going crazy.OK.
你需要放她走
You gotta let her go.
你会没事的
You'll be OK.
听我说
Listen to me.
有时为了保护自己
Sometimes you gotta do what's best for you.
伤害自己爱的人 也是在所难免
Even if it's gonna hurt the one you love.
妈咪 停止吧
Mommy, stop it.
Timmy 再加把劲
Timmy, Kung Fu grip.
妈咪 住手吧 别再伤害别人了
Mommy stop it.Stop hurting people.
你必须离开 永远不要回来
You have to go, never come back.
我会没事的 我保证
I'll be OK, I promise.
我也爱你
I love you too.
所以 这就是所谓的家族事业
So then, this is the family business.
我早就告诉你了 无聊吧
I told you it was boring.
你说的对
Yeah, right.
你也看到了
Well, as you can see.
我离开之后并没有成为摇滚明星
I did not run off to become a rock star.
这我说不好
I don't know about that.
我觉得你现在酷毙了
You look pretty rocking to me.
Dean Winchester
Dean Winchester.
你呢
And what about you.
我以为我会厌烦小镇里
I always thought I would hate being in the same.
千篇一律的生活
Little town my whole life.
比如接管过生意
You know, taking over the diner.
像我爸希望的那样 但是
Like dad always wanted, but.
我并没有厌烦
I don't.
我其实挺喜欢的
I just, I love it.
看来 在我们16岁时
I guess we didn't know everything we thought.
并不像自己想的那么了解自己
We did when we were 16.
并不是完全不了解 只有一些小偏差
Not everything.Just some things.
看来Timmy需要一点帮助来过度
Sounds like Timmy's gonna need some help adjusting.
他有你啊
Yeah, but he's got you.
还像原来一样 讨厌看你离开
Always hate to see you go, D dog.
真是感激不尽
Can't thank you enough for this man.
Sonny 再见
Sonny we will see you around.
再见了 伙计们
You can bet on that boys.Take it easy man.
嘿 你怎么知道
Hey, how do you know.
让Timmy要求他妈走 会有用呢
Timmy asking his mom to leave is gonna work.
我不知道 纯属巧合 好运气
I didn't.Total Hail Mary.Got lucky.
好运气而已吗
You just got lucky.
就像你在这个地方一样
Kinda like what you do with this place.
我以为这里是你生命里最糟糕的一段时间
I mean here I was thinking this is the worst part.
结果却是最好的
Of your life and it turns out to be the best.
那你为什么要走呢
Why would you ever leave.
感觉不对
Never felt right.
真的吗
Really.
就两个月 Sam
It was two months, Sam.OK.
我简直等不急离开这里
I couldn't wait to get out of here.
我不知道要怎么跟你说 那不是我
I don't know what to tell you.It wasn't me.
看啊
Look at you.
- 整的挺干净啊 - 谢谢
- You clean up good - Thank you.
其实
You know what.
我以前从没去过
I've never actually been to.
这种学校舞会
One of those school dances before.
说到这个 你爸在门外
Yeah, about that, Dean, your old man is outside.
这人还真是摸不透
And man he is really something.
我跟他说了
I tried to tell him.
今晚对你很特殊
What a big night it was for you, Dean.
还问他能不能晚点再来
And then ask him if he could come back later.
但是他说只要跟你说 有活儿干了
But he just said to tell you that he had the job.
你就会懂是什么意思的
Said you'd know what that means.
从我出狱后
After I got out of jail.
这个地方给了我第二次机会
This place gave me a second chance.
看来也给了你同样的机会
And it's done the same for you too.
所以 只要你愿意 我会帮你帮到底
So if you want, I'll stick my neck out for you.
给你争取留下来的机会
I will fight for you to stay.
Sonny
Sonny.
谢谢
Thank you for everything.
但是我还是要走
But I have to go.
Dean
Dean.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢什么
For what.
一直在我身边照顾我
For always being there for having my back.
这一路走来不容易
Look the way it hasn't always been easy.
真搞不清楚你在说什么
I don't know what the hell you are talking about.